<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aecepoglu</title>
    <link>https://aecepoglu.com/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aecepoglu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aecepoglu.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advent Of Code 2021 has begun (a while ago)</title>
      <link>https://aecepoglu.com/en/posts/advent-of-code-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aecepoglu.com/en/posts/advent-of-code-intro/</guid>
      <description>I am going to be sharing my solutions for Advent of Code 2021 on my blog; at this page
 I’m going to be using Dyalog-APL this year to solve the problems.
 As I go through each problem I’ll update that article with my solutions.
 At the end of the event I will write a blog-post about my impressions of APL.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021</title>
      <link>https://aecepoglu.com/en/projects/advent-of-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aecepoglu.com/en/projects/advent-of-code/</guid>
      <description>So I have decided to follow Advent-of-Code live this year [I am 10 days behind so it’s hardly live, but I should catch up soon :) ]
 Advent of Code is a programming themed fun-little-event that takes place every year on http://adventofcode.com
 You can find my solutions (in (Dyalog-)APL) below.
   Day 1 https://adventofcode.com/2021/day/1
 q1 ←{ +/ (1↓⍵) &amp;gt; (¯1↓⍵) } q1pt1 ←{ q1 ⍎⍤1⊢↑ ⊃⎕NGET &amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why can&#39;t I see any posts?</title>
      <link>https://aecepoglu.com/en/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aecepoglu.com/en/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Please see http://aecepoglu.com/en/about . The about page describes why this blog exists, what I write about, and what you can expect to show up here in the future.
 I primarily post here in Turkish. The tr button in the navigation menu should take you there or you can click here: http://aecepoglu.com/
 I’ll start putting up some english-only content and translate some of my posts from Turkish soon enough. You can subscribe to my rss-feed to be notified when that happens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://aecepoglu.com/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aecepoglu.com/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
 Welcome to my blog which started off because I had a lot to say in discussions I was having with my colleagues at work and realized that I deliver better in long-form text.
   I write about programming in practice and theory Specifically about new and interesting tech that catches my eyes and that can further serve what I’m now realising is my passion for simplicity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
